climatedepot.com 2012-06-10

# Climate Depot

Privacy Policy 

Climate Depot takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Climate Depot treats personal information that Climate Depot collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Climate Depot products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Climate Depot does not own or control, or to people that Climate Depot does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Climate Depot associated companies such as Google have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by visiting the sites and searching for their privacy policies.   

**Information Collection and Use**

Climate Depot collects personal information when you register with Climate Depot, when you use Climate Depot products or services, when you visit Climate Depot pages or the pages of certain Climate Depot partners, and when you enter promotions, surveys, or sweepstakes. Climate Depot may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Climate Depot and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Climate Depot collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of the services that we offer. Climate Depot automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Climate Depot cookie information, and the page you request. 

Climate Depot uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children**

No one under the legal age of an adult may use Climate Depot' services. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Climate Depot does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Climate Depot under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Climate Depot communicate with you about offers from Climate Depot and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Climate Depot's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if Climate Depot is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Climate Depot will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Climate Depot displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, men ages 35-50 from a particular geographic area. Climate Depot does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. Climate Depot advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). Climate Depot works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

**Cookies**

Climate Depot may set and access Climate Depot cookies on your computer. Climate Depot lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Climate Depot's cookies. Climate Depot uses cookies only inside our network of web sites and in connection with Climate Depot products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

__ You can edit your Climate Depot Account Information at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Climate Depot service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Climate Depot Newsletter, that are considered part of your Climate Depot account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to Climate Depot agents who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Climate Depot may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Climate Depot account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at:

Climate Depot by CFACT  
P.O. Box 65722  
Washington, DC 20035

Phone: 202-429-2737 

Contact us with your questions.
